(Episode 11)
Yu Mi attempted suicide.
What did you say?
Didn't you know that?
I wonder if Jun Seo and Eun Seo
still want to get married.
What can I do for you?
Eun Seo.
Yes.
Bring me some drinks.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to attempt suicide
like a certain someone.
Shin Yu Mi,
how stupid she was.
She didn't even succeed.
I'm not going to die.
I will not.
I will never die.
I'm not going to die before you do.
I will not die before I get to witness
what happy lives you get to lead.
Please don't.
That would be unfair to you
if we were to live happily.
So, please don't forgive us.
Don't forgive me.
Don't forgive me, please.
I will leave now.
Eun Seo.
Choi Eun Seo.
How are you feeling?
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt at all
since you're doing that.
Hold on.
Hello.
Yes, Tae Seok.
Eun Seo fainted. She fainted.
I'm taking her to the hospital.
You can come to...
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, are you there? Are you listening?
Yoon Jun Seo.
You...
Are you with someone?
Tae Seok.
Yu Mi got hurt a lot, so...
It's all right.
I'll take you to the hospital.
I'll take care of you.
Don't worry.
Jun Seo.
Yes.
When you're with me like you are now,
I feel much better.
Will you stay until I fall asleep?
Yes.
Please arrange examinations
for the patient tomorrow.
- Yes.
- What is wrong with her?
It's exhaustion from overwork.
What do you mean by overwork?
How could a person faint like that
from exhaustion from overwork?
She just needs a few more exams tomorrow.
- Give me the examination form.
- Yes.
Here you are.
Why does she need so many examinations?
They would tire her out.
Excuse me.
What have you gone through?
What happened?
Eun Seo fainted. She fainted.
Jun Seo.
Drive safely.
And come back.
I'll be waiting for you.
What happened?
What happened between you and Jun Seo?
Jun Seo said he couldn't come
when you were sick.
He said he couldn't come because of Yu Mi.
What does that mean?
Did you...
break up with Jun Seo?
Is that why you are sick?
Is that why you fainted
when you were with me?
Did you break up with him?
I want to go home. Please let me go.
I want to go home.
How stupid you are. You are fools.
Are you a fool?
Is this what you wanted
after you hurt me so?
What is wrong with you?
What am I supposed to do
if you're like this?
if you two are like this?
What am I supposed to do?
Choi Eun Seo.
You are...
Mom, I'm heading to work now.
Yes.
Mom. I know you don't want to see me.
I know you hate me
for hating your daughter Eun Seo.
But can you look at me at least
when I'm leaving?
Sin Ae.
Come here.
Come.
Sit here.
Sin Ae.
I'm sorry that I haven't been good...
to you.
Mom, you shouldn't be like this.
Please stop lying on your bed.
Didn't you expect this
when you switched Eun Seo and me?
Why are you still like this
when Jun Seo and Eun Seo...
broke up?
Did Eun Seo break up with Jun Seo?
Did Eun Seo...
Eun Seo...
Mom, please stop doing this.
If you keep doing this, it would seem like
things went wrong...
because I came here instead of Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
If I knew it would turn out like this,
I should've let you two meet.
I should've let you see each other.
I shouldn't have been against it.
Don't say that.
I am sorry for not listening to you.
We did wrong.
I'm sorry for hurting you and Dad.
How much of a heartbreak did you suffer?
How much were you hurt?
I'm all right.
I'm fine. Don't feel sorry.
I feel terrible that
I have given you so much pain.
I don't know what I can do.
I'm fine.
It's all right.
I'm good, really.
It is not your fault.
It is not your fault or Dad's fault.
You're late.
You should've switched shifts
since you're not well.
What's this?
It's not like you. What is this about?
Mom, give it to me. I'll do it.
Eun Seo, have you done something?
Have you and your brother...
He's getting married.
What do you mean?
He's getting married to the woman
he was going to.
So, don't worry anymore.
Eun Seo, come here.
Dad.
Thank you...
for changing your mind.
I would like to thank Eun Seo as well.
I do.
It would not have been easy for her.
Yes, I would like to thank her, too.
Perhaps you confused
them for feelings for love...
since you two are so much alike.
Yes.
We were, maybe.
You are very like me.
I knew you would come to your senses...
and do the right thing responsibly.
Time will heal everything.
It will.
Dad.
Please tell me.
You said I am like you.
What would you do if you were me?
Please tell me.
Please tell me how I can be okay.
I...
was going to be with Eun Seo...
even if you and Mom were to get hurt
and everyone was to blame us.
Because I love Eun Seo.
What if I can never be better?
Dad, what can I do?
Please tell me how to stop this pain.
It hurts so much.
(Private View of Yoon Jun Seo)
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
What is it?
No.
I said it's nothing.
It's really nothing worth seeing.
Okay.
Aren't you hungry? I am.
Do you want cup noodles?
That sounds good. Let's go.
I read it all already.
Let's go and eat cup noodles.
Okay.
How have you been?
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
Aren't you even going to look at me?
I can't believe he is having
his private exhibition at your workplace.
He's so cold-hearted, isn't he?
You look at me
only when I mention his name.
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry.
Can you stop saying you're sorry?
Haven't you thought
why I haven't bothered you at all?
I went to Seoul.
I think I might be
kicked out of the family.
Why is that?
I told them I was going to marry you.
I don't worry about
getting kicked out of the family.
I could do golf or art.
I can take care of myself.
But my family is very snobbish.
So, I'm not sure
how you can bear with them.
Nevertheless...
marry me.
I like it. Thank you for your concern.
It might be the most humble one
among all the spaces...
but I do think this suits
your pieces the best.
Yes.
Jun Seo,
why don't you meet Eun Seo
since you're here?
You haven't seen each other
for a while, have you?
No, I haven't.
But I'm afraid I don't have time today.
You don't?
I was surprised when I learned
you had your preview here.
I thought you wouldn't do it.
No, I thought you couldn't do it here.
So, I was a little disappointed.
I'm out of line, aren't I?
It's all right.
I am sorry.
I wanted to see it.
I wanted to see you overcome obstacles,
and never give up.
Are you setting the pieces tomorrow?
Yes.
I should get going.
Good luck with your private view.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I hope more people tell me things like,
"I'm so disappointed," "You're a bad man,"
"How could you do that?"
I'd like to hear that rather than
"I can understand."
See you around.
Hello.
Yes, Yu Mi.
Yes, it's me.
I just checked out the venue.
You chose the good one.
Yes, I like it.
Do you?
If you don't like doing it
at that hotel...
It's okay.
I don't mind.
Okay. I got it.
I will get some fruit.
Yes, see you in a bit.
- How have you...
How have you been?
I heard you were sick.
It was just a cold.
Was it bad?
No.
I'm fine now.
I see.
Why don't you drink your coffee?
- It will get cold.
- Right.
Eun Seo, did you get sick...
because you waited for me that day?
That day.
Jun Seo, I wasn't there, actually.
I didn't go that day, either.
I've also decided to care about myself.
I couldn't go that day.
After what Yu Mi did,
I've been reconsidering things.
And...
I can't beat Yu Mi.
I couldn't ever do what she did.
I couldn't leave with you.
My...
love was...
only about that deep.
Maybe...
it's because we missed each other
so much for a long time,
that we got confused about our feelings.
Yes, that was it.
Yes.
I wish you were right.
I hope so.
It's Tae Seok.
He is so generous to take me back.
He proposed to me.
He said he might get kicked out
of his family.
I don't know what to do,
but I feel apologetic.
But he said I should trust him.
He said he would be good to me.
Eun Seo.
You told me not to be sorry.
But it's not because of what you said.
I want to be happy.
I want to do better this time.
I think I can do it.
Jun Seo, Why don't you say anything?
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Don't you have anything?
I have so much to say to you,
but I can't.
All I want to say to you is...
something I shouldn't say out loud.
Everything is.
I should get going.
You are back, Jun Seo.
You're late.
I only packed the essentials,
but it's still a lot.
I planned to stay until I got well,
but I like it here.
We are going back to the U.S.
after you finish your class.
So, can I stay here until then?
It is not that safe,
and I need to ask Ji Hwan first.
Eun Seo stayed here before.
I will stay.
Have you met Eun Seo?
I know you didn't go to her
when she was in the hospital.
Have you met her?
I met her today.
You did.
I expected it somewhat
when I booked the venue at the hotel.
Yes, I booked it on purpose.
You pretend you're all right,
but you don't seem to be fully here.
I feel like only an empty shell
of you is with me.
I wanted to make sure.
But you ended up meeting her.
Yu Mi,
don't worry.
You are the only one I take care of.
I chose you.
I have to get changed.
(Gallery Sol
Private View of Yoon Jun Seo)
Tae Seok.
I didn't think I could make it later,
so I stopped by to see it
when no one was around.
Weren't you going to meet me?
No.
I know you're blunt,
but it is too much to take now.
I should go.
Tae Seok.
Are you seeing Eun Seo again...
with a good intention?
What did you say?
Eun Seo told me.
I know I have no right to say that.
But I'm asking you.
Is it a good intention?
Did Choi Eun Seo tell you
that we got back together?
Are you sure you're not going to hurt her?
See you later.
Answer me, Han Tae Seok.
Welcome.
Mom.
Excuse me for a moment.
Mom, I'm glad you came.
How much more will you make me worry?
Is he really the only one for you?
I'm glad you are here.
Thank you so much.
Mister.
Are you still calling me mister?
Are you here for Manager Kim?
Yes.
You came to see Jun Seo's Private Preview.
Yes, I stopped by to see her since I came.
You're doing well.
It should be enough to see I'm good.
So, what are you still doing here?
You're distracting me from work.
Just go.
It's been a while. Let me stay longer.
I don't want to waste it.
What are you saying?
Have you paid to see Eun Seo?
Why should I pay?
- Take this.
- It's beautiful.
- I need to get it back right away.
- Why is that?
I'm here for Jun Seo's Private Preview,
and this is for him.
You're so silly.
By the way, this flower bouquet
is exquisite, isn't it?
Change into this.
Dress up. You can't go
to the Private View like that.
I don't understand.
You don't understand.
Did you say you were seeing me again?
I'm sure you have someone
you'd like to show off to...
that we're seeing each other again.
Let's go and meet him.
Tae Seok.
What am I to you?
Am I just that much to you?
Yoon Jun Seo and you.
Don't you care about how I feel...
as long as you don't get Jun Seo hurt?
Do my feelings for you...
mean nothing to you?
Tae Seok.
Wear this.
Don't call me Tae Seok from now on.
I don't want to hear you call me that.
You came. How are you?
I love your paintings.
I'm flattered.
- How is Professor Park?
- He is well.
Please have a drink. Excuse me.
Hello.
- Welcome.
- Thanks.
I've changed my mind.
I was thinking about
what I could do with Eun Seo,
and figured it would be good to come here.
Yes, I'm glad you came.
Would you like a cocktail?
Liquor?
Are you sure
it's okay with you if I have drinks?
Can I have drinks?
You asked that we hang out all night long.
Have them.
She said I could. Let me bring drinks.
What's wrong?
We're getting married soon.
Let's get out.
Tae Seok is acting weird, isn't he?
Are you really seeing him again?
Are you?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Yes, I am, Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Yoon Jun Seo.
What are you doing?
Hello.
I can't believe this.
Eun Seo, go inside.
What did you say?
Where does she think she's going?
What are you saying?
How dare you come here?
Don't you know
what you've done to my daughter?
Ma'am.
- Mom.
- You caused her to almost die.
How could you do this?
Shame on you.
Ma'am.
What are you doing?
Are you taking her side now?
No, I am sorry.
It is my fault. I apologize.
Please excuse us.
Eun Seo.
How rude she is.
Where did she learn such manners?
That is enough.
- Yoon Jun Seo.
- Jun Seo.
I am sorry.
You didn't need to do that.
Don't expect my apology.
I'm not sorry at all.
But of course not.
You and Jun Seo, you two deserve this.
I will bring these clothes
back to your room tomorrow.
I'm relieved.
Jun Seo didn't seem to notice
I lied to him.
Are you really...
Thank you.
I won't put you
in this situation ever again.
I think you have leukemia.
Look at me.
Love?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not your toy.
Yu Mi.
We're going to the U.S. in two months.
Is it an anticancer drug?
You can't die.
Let me help you cure cancer.
Must you return to the U.S.?